cougarfan.com 2013-08-23

# CougarFan.com : Privacy Policy

CougarFan.com is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

Consumer Information  
Data Collection and Opt Out  

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering information to you, CougarFan.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, CougarFan.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by CougarFan.com is used for the purpose of identifying how to best serve our customer.

If you would like additional information about the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by CougarFan.com please [email us](mailto:privacy@cougarfan.com).

In addition, for certain features on CougarFan.com, subscribers are asked to enter explicit personal information.  For the CougarFan Insider email list, an email address is provided.  For interactive game, subscribers are asked to provide name, location and email address.  CougarFan.com uses this information internally to personally identify subscribers, but will never sell this list to any outside company.

**Data Collection and Opt Out**

CougarFan.com, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. CougarFan.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time CougarFan.com serves you a page. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps CougarFan.com remember you and your preferences (like who you are when you login into a game). 

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

If you have any additional questions about CougarFan.com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [privacy@cougarfan.com](mailto:privacy@cougarfan.com).

**Third Parties**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

  © Copyright 1999-2010, CougarFan.com, all rights reserved    
  Maintainer: [webmaster@CougarFan.com](mailto:webmaster@CougarFan.com)
